http://www.grandportage.com/index.php/footer-pages/privacy

Privacy Policy
At Grand Portage Lodge & Casino ("We", "Us", and possessively "Our"), We value your privacy and have posted this Privacy Policy to tell you what information We collect, how We use this information and how We protect it.
TESTIMONIALS YOU SEND US ARE NOT SUBJECT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
IF YOU SEND US INFORMATION REGARDING YOUR EXPERIENCE WITH ONE OR MORE OF OUR PRODUCTS ("YOUR TESTIMONIAL SUBMISSION"), THIS PRIVACY POLICY DOES NOT APPLY TO YOUR TESTIMONIAL SUBMISSION. INSTEAD, PLEASE SEE OUR TERMS OF USE FOR HOW WE MAY USE YOUR TESTIMONIAL SUBMISSION.
INFORMATION WE COLLECT
This Privacy policy governs with respect to each visitor to our website ("You" and possessively "Your") which is located at www.grandportage.com (the "Website") as well as any other microsite, social media application developed by Grand Portage Lodge & Casino (e.g. Facebook application), and/or any other internet services owned or controlled by Grand Portage Lodge & Casino (the Web Site and all other services shall collectively be referred to as the “Service”). In connection with the Service, Our Web servers may automatically recognize and collects Your IP address and, where possible, Your domain name as well as information on which Service pages You access or visit. We may also collect additional non-personally identifiable information, such as pages viewed, browser type, duration and frequency of visits, and other data, and may aggregate any information collected in a manner which does not identify any individual as further described below. Information from You is gathered on Our Service through use of online forms, site-visit data and automatic online collection devices known as "cookies" or “click-stream data”). Cookies are small bits of text that are either used for the duration of a session ("session cookies") or saved on Your computer's hard drive in order to identify You, or information about You, so Your continuing experience with a website over time can be personalized ("persistent cookies"). Session cookies are automatically deleted when You close Your browser; persistent cookies are stored on Your computer until You delete them. As you use the Internet, a trail of electronic information is left at each web site you visit, i.e. “click-stream data”. We may collect and use click-stream data as a form of non-personal information to anonymously determine how much time visitors spend on each page of our Service, how visitors navigate throughout the Service and how we may tailor our web pages to better meet the needs of visitors. All of this non-personal information will be used to improve our Service and our goods and services. Any collection or use of non-personal information including any click-stream data will be anonymous and aggregate, and will not intentionally contain any personally-identifiable information. We do not collect personally identifiable information from You unless You choose to provide it to Us. If You provide Us with Your address or e-mail address, We may use this information to respond to Your message, notify You about updates to Our product offerings, Website, Service, or to contact You for other marketing purposes relating to the products that You requested information about and Our other products or those of our partners or other third parties from time to time. At any time, you may opt-out from receiving any further communications from Us by sending Us an e-mail.
CHILDREN UNDER 21 YEARS OF AGE
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important to Us. For that reason, We do not collect or maintain information from those individuals that We actually know are under 21 years of age, and no part of our Service or advertising has been created or structured to attract anyone under 21 years of age.
WHO HAS ACCESS TO YOUR INFORMATION
WE DO NOT SELL, RENT OR TRANSFER YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION TO ANYONE. Please note that We reserve the right to and may disclose personally identifiable information about you in response to (a) requests from local, state or federal law enforcement officials; (b) any judicial, administrative or similar proceeding or order, such as subpoena; (c) if required by law; or (d) to investigate suspected fraud, harassment, physical threats, or other violations of any law, rule or regulation, the Service rules or policies, or the rights of third parties or to investigate any suspected conduct which we deem improper. Notwithstanding the prohibitions on transfer of your personally identifiable information, We may transfer Your information in connection with a fundamental business change such as a merger, consolidation, or the sale of substantially all of our assets. We utilize third party service providers for certain functions relating to this Service who may have access to Your information. Each such third party provider has a privacy policy at least as restrictive as this Privacy Policy or has contractually agreed to fulfill all obligations provided for in this Privacy Policy.
HOW WE USE PERSONAL INFORMATION
The information We collect from you is an important part of Our ability to offer high-quality products that are relevant to You. Also, from time to time, We may ask for Your opinion or level of interest in certain products. We use this information to customize Your experience with Us and, among other things, to determine which products You would like Us to provide. WE DO NOT SELL YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION - WE USE YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION ONLY AS PERMITTED BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND TO IMPROVE YOUR CUSTOMER EXPERIENCE WITH US. IF YOU SUBMIT INFORMATION TO US REGARDING YOUR EXPERIENCE WITH ONE OR MORE OF OUR PRODUCTS ("YOUR TESTIMONIAL SUBMISSION"), THIS PRIVACY POLICY DOES NOT APPLY TO YOUR TESTIMONIAL SUBMISSION. INSTEAD, PLEASE SEE OUR TERMS OF USE FOR HOW WE MAY USE YOUR TESTIMONIAL SUBMISSION.
HOW WE SAFEGUARD PERSONAL INFORMATION
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of Your information, We have put in place commercially reasonable physical, electronic, and procedural procedures to safeguard and secure the information We have collected from You. However, please be aware that notwithstanding physical, electronic, and procedural procedures to safeguard and secure the information We have collected from You, it is possible that third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications over the Internet. We limit access to Your personal information by Our employees to only those individuals who have a need to use it in the course of performing their job duties.
WE HAVE NO RESPONSIBILITY FOR LINKED WEBSITES OR SOCIAL MEDIA WEB SITES
This Service may contain links to other websites that may provide information about issues, products or services of potential interest to You or may have applications that link from social media web sites such as Facebook or Twitter. Each of these websites may have its own privacy policy governing the collection, use and distribution of information, which may be different than Our Privacy Policy. Accordingly, We do not assume responsibility for information collected, used or distributed by other persons or entities that maintain websites linked to or with this Website or any other liability whatsoever with respect to your interaction or use of these web sites. Furthermore, We do not endorse any such linked website or any products or services available at or through any such linked website.
CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
We may change this Privacy Policy at any time; changes to this Privacy Policy shall be effective immediately upon the posting of such changes. Therefore, You should review this Privacy Policy from time to time.
CONTACTING US REGARDING YOUR PRIVACY
If you have questions or concerns about Our Privacy Policy, Our use of Your information, or if You would like to correct any of Your information in Our records please write to Us at:
Grand Portage Lodge & Casino
P.O. Box 233 Grand Portage, MN 55605
Grand Portage
»   Contact
»   Responsible Gambling
»   Employment
»   Job Openings
»   Apply Now
Let's Get Social!
Free Shuttle - Currently Not Available, Stay Tuned For Updates
©2020 Grand Portage Lodge & Casino. All Right Reserved.
